Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
When I met the one with
my mind of the truth..
Blood,
I'm happy to be a bit shy.
I'm happy to be my one.
If you like me, I'll take
my five to 10, please.
I'm sick, I'm happy to be your first time.
Kill or kiss.
Toxic.
Kill or kiss?
Let's go!
Kill again, kill, kill again!
She's the real head of the Beast Clan?
Then that means Toshiro is...
Well done, but I'll take it from here.
I assume you won't object?
The two of you are such good
boys, knowing not to overstep.
It's the wild dogs who get put down.
By the way, Hikaru, based on what
I've heard, you're looking for a mate.
Something tells me you
wouldn't mind becoming my pet.
As the heads of our families, no
doubt we'll meet again. Who knows?
Maybe the five great families
will move towards unification.
Well, guess we're done here. Huh?
You shift gears fast.
Just what all's left?
I mean, we saved Misadashiyama.
The Beast Clan's plot,
it's not happening now.
Right.
You have a point.
Actually, the hard part, that's up next.
The whole marriage thing.
You know, I'll root for you.
It'll work out.
Hey!
He caught a Gator!
Still in one piece? Somehow. We managed.
I want to thank all of you.
And now you're gonna get the
full taste of our gratitude!
We've prepared a little something.
Modified bloodline increments.
Little critters, thanksgiving
extravaganza! Ingenza!
Rebrand, girl, and become
the cuteness master!
Here it comes, the big climax!
Hit it!
Date!
We hope this expresses
just how grateful we are!
This whole ordeal taught
me a valuable lesson.
Small fry masters like me can put
on a nice show, and that's about it.
But that's fine by me.
I'll still live with my head held up high.
Awesome.
Really, all of you are cool as hell.
Sure are!
It was at that moment
world-class marriage swindler,
Mei Kinosaki, belt the spark
between Gero and Arashiyama.
We're not letting this
opportunity slip by.
Okay, who here saw last
week's Twisted Ropes?
Me, of course.
I didn't know you were also
a die-hard fan of ropes.
Now to steer this conversation.
Speaking of exciting dates, this one
time I went on a private jet ride.
Who are you seeing?
Oil Baron.
Within minutes, I've expertly shifted
the conversation to love and romance.
Boring subject.
Oh, by the way, you haven't told us
what your girlfriend is like, Piichi.
She's the best there is.
Seeing her smile gives me the
courage to take on any job.
And coming home to dinner with
her makes my exhaustion melt away.
When I have a day off,
spending it with her gives me the
strength to handle the days after.
I realize I'm not a decent person.
All of the normal happiness
humans feel that I'm aiming for,
I learned entirely from my girlfriend.
For as long as I live, for better
or for worse, she's the one for me.
In order to protect her,
I would do anything.
I mean it.
Pichi Nakagawa!
You said that without a
hint of embarrassment!
Is this it?
THE POWER OF NATURAL CHARM!
Like a Casanova over
here. Wanna see a picture?
I didn't count on that, but it
certainly turned up the heat.
O-M-G.
That's what it is, fire!
It's time we talked, because
Arashiyama's head over heels for you.
But her feelings?
They're also a double-edged sword.
Since she idolizes you, if the illusion
breaks, things could end like that.
This won't be like Ureshino or Himekawa.
You need to be more careful.
Gedo's grown a lot, so a pep
talk should get him pumped up.
You got it?
All you have to do is play
it cool like Piichi did,
and when the time's
right, get them digits.
Ready to introduce her to
the new and improved Gedo?
Ah, we're almost back to shore.
Well, I guess this means goodbye.
Hi!
Kinosaki-style cording
arts, bridge builder!
I'm sure gonna miss you and
your hammies, Arashiyama.
Yeah, me too. I bet!
That's your cue!
Make your move, kiddo!
I wanted to say...
You mean she likes me?
For real?
You're not pulling my leg?
Why would she like me?
Why would anyone like me?
Come on, focus! Don't freeze up!
Is this because I told
him about her feelings?
Was it too soon?
Look at him!
He can't even construct a word!
He'll never get her number at this rate!
Hikaru-Gero!
What's the matter with
you, cat-got-your-tongue?
Shoot! It's hopeless.
Better put out this fire and
try to salvage whatever's left?
How about I go first then?
I like you.
Did someone say something?
I, uh, like you.
There's just one problem.
I can't be the one who marries you.
Huh?
I overheard you were
looking for a partner.
And thought maybe I had a shot.
But no.
This might sound dumb.
But I'm not good enough.
At least not yet.
I don't feel confident about my work,
and I'm an emotional train wreck.
Even if by some miracle I got you to accept
me, I'd be dependent on you. A burden.
Being dead weight.
That's the last thing I would want.
I'm sorry.
I know this is totally
half-assed and self-centered,
but I'm going to build myself up.
Until I'm crazy independent.
Then I'll confess my feelings again.
You saved my life!
Thank you!
I just did the job I was told to do.
Instead of being the same little girl who
idolized you, I'll become a strong woman.
The kind that can support you.
I'm gonna make you fall for me so hard!
You better be ready!
I bet I sound crazy!
Don't listen to me!
Too late for that.
I don't really know what to say, someone
like you, thinking so much about me.
Never once in my whole life has a
person said anything like that to me.
I'll wait for you.
Yeah? Same.
Until then, would it be okay
if we exchanged numbers?
Sure!
They're a perfect match!
Do it already!
Added, you're in my
contacts now. Same for you.
Well, at least they're hitting it off.
I'm aiming to form the perfect marriage.
For both of them.
Send my fee with the extra
charges to the designated account.
If you miss the payment
deadline, I'll kill you!
Bye-bye?
Did she seem mad?
When did Piichi leave?
He was right here
Welcome back, honey bunches?
It's good to be back, Mary!
How did it go?
It's just group activities
aren't your thing Hmm,
so an overnight on an island with a
bunch of strangers sounds a little rough.
Oh, well, yeah,
it was kind of weird at first, I guess, but
I got along pretty okay with those guys.
Well, is that so?
In that case, sounds like you
ended up making new friends.
Hold on a sec.
Do you think so?
Oh, also, I learned how to
prep and cook a giant squid.
How do you feel about ink pasta?
I love it.
We should add it to the cafe's menu.
Yeah.
So what's next for you, Arashiyama?
Well, I'm glad you asked.
I'm going into business and
starting my own detective agency.
Not the entertainment industry
after that show you put on for us?
It was incredible.
Being a detective is
so much cooler, though.
Besides, I want to find out where
my big brother disappeared to.
See you around.
Arashiyama.
She's great, but she's not the only one.
Himekawa.
Ureshino, too.
They're all beyond amazing, and
they've all been putting the work in.
I need to do the same
and be way more charming.
I'll be a man who's worthy of their love!
Then I'll whip you into shape with my
patented training of a thousand doormans!
Please do.
Good evening, Taduaki.
How's our new poison that treating you?
Is it everything you hoped for?
I nearly died, and I've never been better.
So, teacher, what can I do for you?
It's concerning Master Hikaru's marriage.
Tell me more.
I've got good vibes
from all three of them.
There's my boss at work,
a guy my age from a different school,
and an underclassman I met
at a club in junior high.
There's no way I could
pick only one of them,
seeing as how I love each of them to bits.
Help me out, advisor.
What should I do?
I see your problem.
Now all three of them want to take
me out on a date for my birthday.
Oh, really?
But you know...
Romantic counseling?
Yep.
May the love evangelist, followers
only, kiss your worries goodbye.
Next time, while I'm doing my side hustle,
I want you to sit in on the sessions.
Why would I ever...
Is this it? My practice?
To max my charm?
It went over Himekawa,
Ureshino, and Arashiyama?
The training of a thousand torments.
I've endured a hundred
already only nine hundred left
I say bring it on
So what am I supposed to do now? Well,
this is just a suggestion
But why don't you triple
book so you can hang out
with all three of them?
I never thought of that
Thanks a bunch good luck
either you so about my birthday
Please let that be the toughest one. Yo!
Before school ends, I've got
to ask out the team manager!
Only all the other players like her too!
But no one's feelings for
her are stronger than mine!
How do I score the final
try and win over her heart?
You should field this one.
For starters, be yourself
around her. What else?
Be polite. Got it!
Thanks, coach!
Good luck!
Hmm!
Break time.
The bathroom's sparkling clean! Who?
Is it a magic trick?
Was my advice good enough?
Okay, break's done.
Now back to work.
At first, I only saw it as a fling,
but now it feels so much more real.
Ever since graduating from college,
I've been swamped with work.
I haven't met any nice girls.
For quite a long time i've been
teaching a spanish cooking class.
And one of my students has my
heart dancing a paso double.
Yeah what do you think any feedback on
my song i wrote it for my sweetheart?
I'm wondering whether i should ask
out this girl we're in the same year.
I met an older woman on a trip
i can't get her out of my head.
Five years now under the same roof.
Where's my ring?
I'm madly in love with my
Spanish cooking teacher.
Things are spicy.
We can fit in another 20 today, right?
I've got no choice.
It's my only hope.
Intellectual linguistic
enhancer toxin. Silver tongue!
Whoa, stop that!
Kill yourself just to
get out of counseling!
Admit it, I'm hopeless. I know.
Everybody is fighting their own battles.
How can I possibly give them the
answers they desperately need?
You're doing just fine.
Everyone has to work as hard as you.
I just wanted you to see for yourself.
Honestly, there are no right answers.
Everyone's doing their best in
figuring out their own situation.
Deciding what's best for themselves.
Do you remember the other day?
When Arashiyama said she liked you, it
was like you lost all your confidence.
Your expression said, I can't accept
her feelings the way I'd like to.
But you see, that just proves
you're like everyone else.
And you're giving your love
life all you've got, too.
Baby steps.
Don't give up.
Because you're on the right path.
Don't get me wrong, though.
You still have a long way to go.
Thank you very much.
One sec. Huh?
Huh?
Best of luck out there.
Same.
Why the candy kit?
I'm rewarding myself.
What?
Let's really celebrate
with sukiyaki! Sorry.
I've actually got plans.
How about a rain check?
Fine, but you owe me fancy sukiyaki and
sushi for the after party, got that?
Kinosaki. Hmm?
I want to say, even since the first
day I met you strapped to that chair,
and you agreed to help me by
becoming my marriage advisor,
we've been through a whole lot.
And, well, the truth is,
no matter what we dealt with, I
had a great time through all of it.
I mean, before I met you, the best
thing I had going for me was this.
DIY candy kits.
What I'm saying is?
I hope you'll continue guiding me.
in my search for a bride.
Ghetto.
Just leave it to me.
I'll make sure it happens.
You're going to end up happily married.
I guarantee it.
Hikaru, it's been way too long.
Thanks for making time for me tonight!
So how's the search?
Pretty okay, I guess What?
You mean it's going well?
That advisor must be a miracle worker.
You could have a little more faith in me!
Still, you might have to hurry.
There's a rumor about the
ghetto branch families.
Dark.
He's up to something.
Warn people!
I혜.
Oh.
In the way, I'm scared to go.
I thrilled that you'll know.
But I'm the only one who's doing it.
The bottom is the tone of the skin.
Oh, baby boy.
Oh, you don't have a skin.
Ah, I'm the one who's doing it.
I'm the one
who's doing it.
Bye bye, you? . . . .
We'll see
you
next
time.